watchindiandramas.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy

  * Tuesday, December 6, 2011, 9:47

## Google Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is for watchindiandramas.com

We allow third-party advertising companies (like [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense/)) to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Here are some third-party vendors serving ads on this site and you may visit those vendor websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor offers this capability).

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info_at_watchindiandramas_dot_com

At watchindiandramas.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by watchindiandramas.com and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, watchindiandramas.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
http://watchindiandramas.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://watchindiandramas.com

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to http://watchindiandramas.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

  * 

#### About the Author

has written 3583 stories on this site.

it is zeshan and he is the software worker and working on this site which is Honorable thing for him....

## Write a Comment

Gravatars are small images that can show your personality. You can get your [**gravatar**](http://gravatar.com/) for free today!

You must be [logged in](http://watchindiandramas.com/wp-login.php?redirect_to=http%3A%2F%2Fwatchindiandramas.com%2Fsample-page) to post a comment.
